Yong-chan Park

Ph.D. Student at Seoul National University

wjdakf3948@snu.ac.kr (+82)-2-880-7263

About Me

I am a Ph.D. student majoring in Computer Science and Engineering at <u>Seoul National University</u> (SNU), advised by <u>Prof. U Kang</u> in <u>Data Mining Laboratory</u>. My research interests include machine learning and time series analysis. I am currently investigating a novel decomposition method for arrays, with a sequential analogy of Taylor's Theorem.

Research Interests

Machine learning, Deep learning, Time series analysis

Education

Ph.D. Student Mar. 2020 - Present

- Computer Science and Engineering, SNU

Bachelor of Science

- Department of Mathematical Sciences, SNU

Research Experiences

A novel approach to Fourier Transform [1]

June 2020 - Present

Mar. 2012 - Feb. 2019

- Propose Partial Fourier Transform (PFT) that rapidly computes a part of Fourier coefficients of a given time series and demonstrate the accuracy and efficacy of PFT on real-world anomaly detection [1]. PFT achieves 20x faster running time compared to SOTA algorithms.
- Patent pending

Stock movement prediction [2]

Sep. 2020 - Present

- Propose Data-Axis Transformer with Multi-Level Contexts (DTML) for stock movement prediction that learns the correlations between stocks in an end-to-end way [2]. DTML achieves SOTA accuracy on six datasets collected from US, China, Japan, and UK.

Software development for patent management

Sep. 2020 - Present

- Implement LSH (Locality Sensitive Hashing) algorithm for finding similar patent data, and a BERT-based model for automatic patent classification.
- Develop a GUI with additional functionality of visualizing results.
- Industry-Academy Cooperation with Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering Co., Ltd.

Publications

- [1] **Yong-chan Park**, Jun-Gi Jang, and U Kang. "Fast and Accurate Partial Fourier Transform for Time Series Data." KDD 2021
- [2] Jaemin Yoo, Yejun Soun, <u>Yong-chan Park</u>, and U Kang. "Accurate Multivariate Stock Movement Prediction via Data-Axis Transformer with Multi-Level Contexts." KDD 2021
- [3] <u>Yong-chan Park</u>*, Sangjun Son*, Minyong Cho, and U Kang. "DAO-CP: Data-Adaptive Online CP Decomposition for Tensor Stream." PLOS One 2022 (*equal contribution)
- [4] Jun-Gi Jang, Jeongyoung Lee, <u>Yong-chan Park</u>, and U Kang. "Fast and Accurate Dual-Way Streaming PARAFAC2 for Irregular Tensors Algorithm and Application." KDD 2023

Services

Reviewer @ KDD 2022 Reviewer @ NeurIPS 2021